Customs and border -protection officials are seeing a rise in people illegally
bringing eggs from Mexico into border states such as Texas.
Customs border -protection officials are seeing a rise in people illegally bringing
eggs from Mexico into border states such as Texas.
The U.S.
average price for a dozen large eggs last month hit $4.25.
That's more than double their $1.78 price in December 2023.
The U.S.
average price for a dozen large eggs last month hit $4.25.
That's more than double their $1.78 price in December 2023.
The U.S.
average price for a dozen large eggs last month hit $4.25.
That's more than double their $1.78 price in December 2023.
Meanwhile, 30 eggs in Mexico sell for just $3.40.
Those bringing eggs into the U.S.
risk fines of up to $10,000.
Meanwhile, 30 eggs in Mexico sell for just $3.40.
Those bringing eggs into the U.S.
risk fines of up to $10,000.
But officials say they usually seize and destroy the eggs.
They also impose a $300 penalty.
The Department of Agriculture banned eggs from Mexico in 2012.
But officials say they usually seize and destroy the eggs.
They also impose a $300 penalty.
The Department of Agriculture banned eggs from Mexico in 2012.
But officials say they usually seize and destroy the eggs.
They also impose a $300 penalty.
The Department of Agriculture banned eggs from Mexico in 2012.
This was due to the risk of bird flu.
Officials said most people...